Excuse me.
Is it at all possible
that you're knitting
a pair of pants?
Oh, well, no, you're
understandably terrified.
But, you know,
allow me to explain.
45 days ago, um,
I embarked on
a railroad journey
of healing
because my university
was making me do
string theory,
and my favorite comic
book store burned down,
and when my roommate
got engaged,
my girlfriend wanted
to move in with me,
which was no doubt
a ploy just to see my--
well, excuse my language,
but my bathing suit parts.
Uh, sir, may I
use your phone?
I don't think so.
Yeah, well,
I understand that
I'm half naked,
but there is
a reasonable explanation.
While I slept
in my sleeper car,
all my possessions were stolen.
Now,
typically,
I wear pajamas,
but I recently adopted
a hobo lifestyle
and pajamas are the
sleep-pants of the Man.
I'll have you know,
Mahatma Gandhi wore no pants
and a nation rallied behind him!
My good man...
Now, before you walk away...
I know that I may
appear deranged,
but I am, in fact,
a world-renowned physicist.
Ask me the difference
between a boson and a fermion.
Go ahead, ask!
Bosons have integer spin,
fermions have half-integer spin!
My legs are getting cold!
Why won't anybody help me?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 8x01 ♪
The Locomotion Interruption
Original Air Date on Septembe
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(sniffs)
Morning.
Hi. Want to do
yoga with me?
Um, let me just have
some coffee first,
and then I'll have
the strength to tell you
how much I won't be doing that.
(Phone rings)
Hello?
Hello, Leonard.
Hey, buddy.
Good to hear your voice.
Uh, I'm in Kingman, Arizona,
and, uh, I need you
to come pick me up.
I'd love to.
I'm just about
to do yoga with Penny.
Leonard, I'm at
the police station.
I was robbed.
Th-They took my phone,
my wallet, my iPad, everything.
Oh, my God, are you okay?
No,
I'm not okay.
I-I'm wearing borrowed pants,
I-I don't have I.D.,
and one of the officers here
won't stop calling me
Chicken Legs.
Okay.
Uh, I'll-I'll
come get you.
What's the address?
Hey, what's going on?
Oh.
He got all of
his stuff stolen.
Oh...
Okay...
Sheldon, hang tight.
Hey, do you want me
to bring anything?
Oh, yes, please.
A pair of pants.
And my toothbrush.
Yeah, and my mail.
And a really good comeback
for Chicken Legs,
because “I know you are,
but what am I?”
was met with stony silence.
I'll be there
as soon as I can.
Is he okay?
Yeah, he's fine, he's
just a little rattled.
Oh...
Feel like driving
to Arizona with me?
I can't, I have
that job interview.
Oh, right.
Besides,
I don't need six hours of
“Your hair is different.
“Why did you change your hair?
I'm holding my breath
until your hair grows back.”